Let's do a critical thinking exercise.
Look at Jedi.
No, we don't believe you.
Everyone around Jasmine is racist and bigots.
So what do you expect her to do?
To move forward as a politician to reach the highest level, people end up having to sacrifice someone.
You can sit here and chat your mouth off because you're not running for any office.
You can talk reckless and speak your mind.
It's chess, not checkers.
You're obviously playing checkers.
This is someone named Freck and Locke.
Now, I don't think she's the only person who thinks this way, but as a critical thinking exercise,
I would love to hear you guys' thoughts in the comments on this assessment of politics
and of how we as the people should be engaging with those who are in the political class.
Do we agree with Freck and Locke that it is acceptable for the folks that we are engaging in
or expecting to represent us to behave in this fashion?
Do we think that a sector that operates in this way is one that we would ever have any actual
efficacy in, any actual representation in?
Do we think that this type of setup is one that is sustainable or that we should continue to sustain?
Let me know your thoughts in the comments.